Vod2smi by Blue-Bird™
Bast...
time is running out.
Please allow me to heal
my brother of this illness,
and I will never
question your existence again.
His heart rate is dropping
fast. Where are we?
We are finishing
a sequence now.
- GRIOT,
give me the controls.
- As you wish, Princess.
What is the confidence rate?
- 25%.
We'll have to try another way.
King T'Challa's heart rate
has fallen to 31 beats
per minute.
Princess,
you should go be by his side.
I have to think.
Everyone, get out.
Get out!
What is the confidence rate?
- 29.1%.
Print it!
- Princess,
I am aware of the urgency,
but I must warn you,
this synthetic
Heart-Shaped Herb
has a minimal chance of
producing the desired effects.
I don't care! Has to work.
GRIOT.
- Yes, Princess?
What's my brother's
heart rate?
Your brother
is with the ancestors.
No.
- Praise the ancestors.
T'Challa, T'Challa, T'Challa
T'Challa
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- It is an honor for me...
to invite her majesty,
Queen Ramonda,
daughter of Lumumba,
sovereign ruler
of the kingdom of Wakanda.
Mr. Chairperson,
I believe I speak for
all the member states here
when I say that
I am deeply disappointed
in Wakanda's failure
to stand by promises to
participate in global efforts
to tackle
international challenges,
to share resources,
and full cooperation
concerning vibranium.
I now give the floor
to Her Majesty, Queen Ramonda.
It has always been our policy
to never trade vibranium
under any circumstance.
Not because of the dangerous
potential of vibranium,
but because of the dangerous
potential of you.
You perform civility here.
But we know what you whisper
in your halls of leadership
and in your
military facilities.
"The King is dead.
"The Black Panther is gone.
"They have lost
their protector.
- "Now is our time...
"to strike."
Aneka, where is your spear?
Shuri gave me these to try.
You know, I like them better.
- Our foremothers
gave us the spear...
because it is precise,
elegant...
and deadly.
It will not change
under my watch.
Yes, General.
I told you not to bring them.
Last night
there was another attack
on one of
our outreach facilities.
Proof of the involvement
of a member state
is being uploaded to your
mobile devices as we speak.
And as for the identity
of the attackers...
Let our gracious
response to this incursion
be an olive branch.
Further attempts
on our resources
will be considered
an act of aggression
and met with
a much steeper response.
We mourn the loss of our king.
But do not think for a second
that Wakanda
has lost her ability
to protect our resources.
We are aware
of the ongoing efforts by some
to find vibranium
outside of Wakanda,
and wish you the best of luck.
-
This is Rotor 625
requesting clearance to land.
DR.- All right.
Meet you down there.
Yeah.
Hey!
I thought you retired!
I thought I had too.
They said that machine
had a one in a billion chance
of finding vibranium.
Oh, less than that.
Here we go.
Cabin pressure is stable
at negative one P-S-I.
At 800 feet,
passing through thermocline.
All my life supports
in the green.
Copy you.
- We've touched down.
DR.-
Perfect. So, Salazar,
you are near the site
right there.
- Yeah,
it's astonishing.
The drill
seemed to make contact
with a metallic substance.
- Whatever it is,
it's solid.
I've never seen a drill bit
chewed up like this before.
- I'll be.
Vibranium in the ocean.
Let's go ahead and get
the detector out of there,
since it's the only one
we've got.
- Heading towards
the vibranium detector.
Okay, Salazar,
we just went dark.
- Yeah.
The rig lost power.
Copy that.
I'm gonna fix it up here.
- What the hell was that?
- Jackson,
tell me you're seeing this?
DR.- Hang on.
Salazar's heart rate.
Hey, uh, Salazar,
can you give me a visual?
It's a phantom jellyfish.
I've never seen one
this color.
Emergency dive team, stand by.
Salazar, uh,
we just lost Jackson's vitals.
Can you see him?
No. He's gone.
Can you clarify? What do
you mean by, "He's gone"?
Salazar, do you copy?
-Salazar?
- Smitty,
we got a situation out here.
What's that sound?
West, you got a visual
on what's making that sound?
West, how copy, over?
West, you got a visual?
- It's some kind
of sonic attack.
Hey, Smitty, earplugs.
We are under attack.
You need to send in
a strike team immediately.
Copy. Mayday, mayday,
this is Rotor 625.
We are requesting
assistance immediately.
It's the Wakandans.
It has to be.
Henderson.
Smitty, we gotta go.
Henderson!
Let's go.
What's going on?
Get off the edge.
Go, go, go, go!
Now! Go!
Spin! Spin them off!
Okay. They're gone!
-Oh, my God!
DR.- Just get us out.
- We're good.
-We're good.
Where is the strike team?
It wasn't the Wakandans.
They... They were blue.
Everyone is dead...
Shit. What is going on?
- We're getting
pulled backwards.
Oh, my God.
-Oh, God! Hang on!
- Queen Ramonda
of the nation of Wakanda
gave an electrifying speech
at the UN yesterday,
while members of her military
escorted
captive mercenaries
onto the floor of the UN.
A year has passed
since Queen Ramonda
was reinstated
as ruler of Wakanda
after King T'Challa's
sudden death
from an undisclosed illness
last year.
All eyes are on the tiny,
powerful nation,
as it finds itself
increasingly isolated...
Approaching the river border.
We are home.
- Princess.
Just a moment.
I'm in the middle
of something.
- I understand,
Princess, however...
You're disrupting
my train of thought.
- Shuri.
Mother.
- I was trying
to tell you.
The Queen is here.
-Thank you.
-That thing unnerves me.
I think that one day
artificial intelligence
is going to kill us all.
My AI isn't like the movies,
Mother.
It does exactly
what I tell it to do.
Yeah, if only children
were the same.
Everyone seems to be
working diligently.
Yes. Rapid emergency
response task.
There could be any number of
unknown threats
on the horizon,
and they're
creating solutions.
- Oh, what is this?
Exo Suits for our army.
It grants the user
super-human strength,
speed, and durability.
But, as always,
Okoye had notes.
What were her notes?
She hates them.
Oh.
What about recreating
the Heart-Shaped Herb?
Have you made
any progress on that?
- Excuse me, Princess.
Nakia, daughter of Yaa,
is trying to reach you again.
Maybe you should...
Maybe you should
continue your calculations
as I instructed.
- As you wish, Princess.
We do not need the Herb,
Mother.
We need new technology.
What of the Black Panther?
The mantle has unified
our nation for centuries.
The Black Panther
is a relic, Mother.
I wasn't trying to save
the mantle with the Herb,
I was trying
to save my brother.
- Oh, Shuri.
Do you know what day it is?
Tuesday.
The date, child.
Brother's passing.
One year ago today.
Have you planned anything?
Yes. It involves you taking
your mother for a drive.
-Right now?
-Right now.
And you can leave
your Kimoyo Beads here.
-Mother.
-No, no.
You won't need them
where we are going.
Hmm?
And the other two. Yes.
You need to sit here with me.
And with yourself.
It is the only way
you are going to heal
from the wound caused
by T'Challa's death.
I'm fine, Mother.
You don't have to worry
about me.
He's gone,
but I'm moving forward.
T'Challa is dead,
but that doesn't mean
he is gone.
When that illness
took your brother from us,
I had to lead a wounded nation
and a broken world.
But I still took time
in the bush.
I wandered
until I found water.
And I sat.
Then I did this ritual
that I am about
to show you now.
I found your brother
in the breeze,
pushing me gently, but firm.
Like his hand on my shoulder.
It took some time,
but he was there.
He wasn't there, Mother.
The presence that you felt
was just a construct
of your mind.
Brought on so you could feel
some comfort or joy.
That's all.
Hmm.
What construct
does your mind create
when you think
of your brother?
Does it offer you comfort?
Or torment?
Come, child.
How did you get this?
What does it matter?
What does this have to do
with your ritual?
- Burning
of the funeral garments
marks the end
of the mourning period
and the beginning
of a new relationship
with our loved ones
that have passed on...
I'm not doing this, Mother.
If I sit
and think about my brother
for too long,
it won't be these clothes
I'll burn.
It will be the world...
and everyone in it.
Shuri...
Shuri, there's something
that I need to tell you
about your brother.
Mother, wait!
-What are you doing?
This better not be
a part of your ritual.
It isn't.
- Stop! Right there!
Who are you?
And how did you get in here?
This place is amazing.
The air is pristine.
And the water...
My mother told stories
about a place like this.
A protected land with people
that never have to leave.
That never have to change
who they were.
What reason do you have
to reveal your secret
to the world?
I am not a woman
who enjoys repeating herself.
Who are you?
- I have many names.
My people call me
K'uk'ulkan...
but my enemies call me Namor.
The American military
detected vibranium
under my nation's domain.
I was able to
stop them from minin' it,
but we need Wakanda's help
to prevent it
from happenin' again.
They use a machine designed
by an American scientist.
Vibranium only exists here.
In Wakanda.
Mother, he's covered in it.
Your son exposed the power
of vibranium to the world.
In response,
other nations have begun
searching the planet for it.
His choice has compromised us.
I think Wakanda
could find the scientist
and bring them to me?
It is only fair that Wakanda
helps to resolve our dilemma.
You do not sneak
into my country
and tell me what is fair.
I have more soldiers than
this land has blades of grass.
And they have
incomparable strength.
I would hate to come back
under different circumstances.
When you have the scientist,
blow into this,
place it in the ocean.
I'll be there
shortly afterwards.
For your own sake,
don't mention
anything about me
to anyone outside of Wakanda.
Did you see the wings
on his ankles?
- How did he do that?
We must convene the Council.
- Heaven Scrapers
had no evidence
of any activity at all.
Oh, the river border
has been breached, huh?
If my soldiers were present,
this "fish man"
would be bound before us
as we speak.
If your muscle brains
were present,
they would still be there
choking on their
fuzzy adornments.
You bald-headed demon...
Show some respect, you two.
M'- Respect?
These men should be
ashamed to show their faces!
Watch your tone, Jabari!
- As I was saying,
there was no aerial
surveillance footage of him.
And nothing
on the radar as well.
So, he swam underwater
for 100 kilometers.
- He was not alone.
And claims to command
a massive army.
He wants us to deliver
one American scientist?
So he can kill them?
Do it.
We never had to face an enemy
with access
to vibranium before.
And we have no Black Panther
to protect us.
M'- That is because
this wise Council
allowed Killmonger
to take the throne
and burn up all of your
precious Heart-Shaped Herb.
M'Baku,
what would you have us do?
We should find the fish man
and kill him.
If we do
what he is asking for now,
what is to stop him
from coming back
and asking for more?
- As you were.
Is it just me, or does this
keep getting uglier?
It's you.
-So, does it work?
-Yes.
This thing can detect
the altered frequency
of vibranium
through water, stones,
even heavy metals.
Whoever built this
is brilliant.
Come, look.
Some are custom parts
and others look like
they gathered it
from a junkyard.
I am still struggling
to believe
that vibranium exists
outside of Wakanda.
Perhaps there was
more than one meteorite.
Our planet is covered
of mostly water,
so it's reasonable
that the other one
just landed there.
This changes everything
that we know.
The Great Mound.
All of the legends and fables.
Those stories
are seared in my mind.
That sounds very painful.
So we have to find
this scientist after all.
-I do have an idea.
-- Mm.
I'm going to need
the princess.
Out of the question.
She is in no state
to be in the field.
it may
do her some good to get out.
It might just be exactly
what she needs.
Besides, I can do
this American operation
with my eyes closed.
It's not the Americans
that I'm worried about.
This Namor,
he snuck past our defenses.
That will never happen again.
He was not alone.
She'll be with me.
- So,
when are we leavin'
so I can see
my favorite colonizer?
Can't stop
-Addicted to the shindig
Chop Top,
he says I'm gonna win big...
Whoa.
Distant cousin
to the reservation
Defunkt the pistol
that you pay for
This punk, the feeling
that you stay for...
Come on.
Yeah, I got it.
I got it.
Will you slow down?
You didn't think to call?
Now, why would I have
your number?
We are looking
for the scientist
who built
the vibranium detector.
So it was you guys
in the Atlantic?
Come on. Mining ship.
Lot of casualties.
What happened?
Seriously?
It was a joint operation.
Us and the SEALs.
Thirty of their top guys,
two of our best officers,
friends of mine.
Gone.
Just like that.
You throw in the fact
that they were tracking
vibranium...
I can assure you Wakanda
had nothing to do with this.
So who was it?
God, look, the way that
this is supposed to work
is that I give you information
and you reciprocate.
For our own safety,
we cannot tell you.
It's imperative that
we get to the scientist
before anything else happens.
You owe me, Ross.
You owe my brother.
Okay, look.
There are agents who have
been sentenced to death
for less than
I'm about to give you now.
And we got a new director.
She's watching me like a hawk.
We will be very, very careful.
Not just careful,
you gotta be fast.
The US needs another machine
and this kid is
the only person in the world
who knows how to build one.
So they're comin' for her.
A kid?
-Hey.
-You forgot to Venmo me.
Ah, it slipped my mind.
It's eight hundred, right?
Eight hundred
was yesterday's price.
It's a band today.
That's predatory. I...
I built the whole
robotic hand.
You just corrected
the grip algorithm.
And what grade did you get?
Thanks.
Is that an iPhone I see?
- Primitive.
We have located the scientist.
She is
in the American equivalent
of a Wakandan village school.
- A school?
Please tell me
it is a professor.
It's a student, Mother.
We can't give her to Namor.
- Bring this student
back to Wakanda.
I've got it from here.
Wait. Maybe I should
speak with her.
It will be more discreet.
I can be discreet.
What?
-Nothing.
-Is it the makeup?
No.
It's the wrong shade,
isn't it?
It's the right shade.
Fenty 440. You look good.
I can blend in as a student.
I can do this.
-You get five minutes.
-Yes!
- Yo!
Riri Williams?
Yo, I don't do drop-bys
no more.
You gotta go to the website.
It's an encrypted file.
I wanted to airdrop it.
You the...
Whew.
You're Princess Shuri.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Oh, shit,
am I getting recruited?
No.
I'm here about
the vibranium detector
that you built for the CIA.
I ain't built no detector
for no CIA.
I made that
for my metallurgy class.
-A school project?
-- Yeah.
My professor said
I'd never be able to do it.
To be young, gifted,
and Black though, right?
Y'all probably don't say that
in Wakanda.
How old are you?
Nineteen.
Brilliance at a young age
is not always accepted
by the elders.
How long did it take you?
Couple months.
-Couple months?
-The hardest part was
finding big enough
mylar sheets to cover the...
Wait, did I piss off Wakanda?
Not just us.
This place is no longer safe
for you.
Gather your things
and come with me. Right now.
I got Differential Equations
class in, like, 15 minutes.
Okay.
You wait right here.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
I'm just gonna...
Ooh!
- I had it under control.
I said five minutes.
I gave you six.
Get out. Get out of my dorm.
Get out!
Hey.
I'm warning you!
Do not take another step
-toward me!
-Oh!
See how they teach
the children
to treat their guests? Mm!
Oh...
You brought a spear in here?
You brought a spear in here.
I like her.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
-Put it down, put it...
-- Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
You'll hurt yourself. Come on.
- It's all right, Princess.
Small, small girl.
I am going to give you
two options.
You can come to Wakanda,
conscious or unconscious.
You need to be conscious
of the way that you look.
Walking round here,
all that ash on your head.
-Oh, it's funny?
-No, it's not.
-Mm-hmm. I told you!
-You look good.
Calm down.
We'll leave, okay?
And she can deal
with that merman
with the winged ankles
who wants to kill her
all by herself.
-You got this.
-Mm, with your heater.
-- Come on. Let's go.
What?
- What exactly
is this place?
- I fixed a few trucks
for the head of sanitation.
He lets me work out
of this garage in exchange.
I just have to grab
my work laptop.
Please don't touch anything.
- You don't have to worry
about that.
- It may not
look like much,
but it's my life's work
in here.
- Mm-hmm.
So, the design for the machine
is on that laptop?
Yeah.
And you just leave it
on a desk in a car garage?
I got 2065-byte encryption
on that thing.
That's impressive.
Ever locked yourself out?
- Took me the whole
semester to get back in.
Had to build a functional
quantum computer
just to crack
my own encryption.
What is it you're building
here? Is it Stark Tech?
I said don't touch anything.
- Princess,
American law enforcement
has arrived at your location.
-- Shit.
-Who was that?
My AI.
They are surrounding us.
I thought you said a merman
was after me.
That's the feds.
Oh, I do not need this shit
right now!
I swear to God,
I was doing so well!
Goin' to class on time.
I must be dumb as hell.
Real dumb thinking that
the Princess of Wakanda
is gonna show up
at my doorstep
and then shit
about to pop off.
I think
that I'm actually gonna take
my chances with this merman,
because at least he never
brought the FBI to my garage!
Hey. Namor sank an entire ship
of CIA operatives...
This is the Federal Bureau
of Investigation.
...because of
your little machine.
So those popo out there...
- We have
surrounded the premises.
...are the very least
of your worries.
Listen, we need to work
together to get out of here.
General,
they've got us surrounded.
Maybe we should just split up.
Out of the question.
Does this vehicle work?
No.
Everything in this lab works.
Including this bike.
Don't even think about it.
Besides,
there are three of us.
Two of y'all. I'm takin' this.
- Whoo!
I knew it.
Don't tell me that
you built this in two months.
I spent years
on this. On and off.
-Nice. Have you flown it yet?
That thing can fly?
There's an entire
YouTube channel
dedicated to sightings of me.
- That's awesome.
- We have
a warrant to detain...
-- Come.
-...the student Riri Williams.
Wireless transmitter,
so we can communicate.
Don't try to scurry off.
- General Okoye,
Princess Shuri,
come out with your hands up.
- What a hunk of junk.
Hey, please be careful.
- You will not
be placed under arrest.
Keys are on the seat.
Once we get to
the other side of the bridge,
we can lose them
in Boston traffic.
General,
we really need to split up.
Listen to me.
We are not in your lab.
We are in the field.
Now, get her in the car.
Always shouting at me.
- The tactical unit
will breach the entrance
in three, two,
-one.
- FBI! Don't move!
- What the hell is that?
Oh, shit!
She got an Iron Man suit?
-Fall back!
-Stay where you are!
- Guess it can fly.
- GRIOT!
- Yes, Princess.
-Now!
-Remote piloting activated.
- Shuri! No!
Clip, pole, smoke, fade
They want the drip
Let's go!
- GRIOT.
Give me a visual.
They want the glow
They want my soul
They want the wave
I keep a clip
I keep a pole
Who want the smoke
Who want the fade
- GRIOT...
- Yes, General?
...take me to the princess
or I will drive my spear
so deep into your CPU,
you will not
be able to process
basic input for a millennia.
- Just one moment,
General.
- Okoye,
I'm on my way to you.
Bounce, crouch or get slouched
My whole hood devout
My mama taught me
not to be a harlot
My granny help me
take the wise route
Although I'm itty bitty
sitting pretty
GRIOT, give me control
of this vehicle right now!
- I am clearing you
a path.
She's all yours, General.
Manual drive engaged.
Look, I know you on my bumper
I know you want my thunder
Why the laws
wanna take us under
We need to find
an extraction point.
- There's one
across the river.
I know you want my thunder
Why the laws
wanna take us under
Why the hell
am I in this jungle
Hey, yo, they cuttin' off
the bridge.
- Princess,
there is a surveillance drone
-locked onto you.
-How high?
- Thirty-thousand feet.
We don't cry 'bout
how they try take us all out
-Look
-They want the drip
They want my soul
Hang on.
I got it.
Come on, Riri.
You gotta find
these differential equations.
Once the relative velocity
evens out...
- Riri, I'm not sure
you can reach that drone
without an oxygen mask.
- Oxygen level
is now 55%.
- Twenty-eight
thousand feet.
- Oxygen level
is now 30%.
Maximum acceleration.
I just need to adjust
my Euler angles
and that should...
that should drop it
right on the...
- Oxygen, 0%.
The drone is no longer
tracking you.
Altitude,
500 feet and falling.
Riri! Are you okay?
-Riri!
-Yeah.
I'm good.
- Incoming!
- Get out of the way!
-Shit!
-- And no worries.
I got a special delivery
for y'all in three,
two, one...
- Nice one, Riri!
We got the glow
We got the soul
We got the wave
- Whoo!
-- Riri!
What just happened?
Shuri!
- The Princess's vitals
are stable, General.
She should regain
consciousness momentarily.
Take another step closer
and I will kill you all.
Drop your weapons!
Hey, is she blue?
-
Drop your weapon!
- Okoye!
Wait!
- Activating
interpretation.
-I'm Shuri.
Princess of Wakanda.
I demand that you take me
to Namor.
Do not bring harm
to this girl.
Do we take them both alive?
-- Yes, Attuma.
- Breathe.
Shuri!
Ross, from the Agency.
You got any witnesses?
None. But we think
it was the Wakandans.
Excuse me?
Our field office
got a tip from Langley
that they were coming.
Right. Who made that call?
-She did.
-- Director de Fontaine.
Director de Fontaine.
Really?
Well...
Uh, Agent thinks
it was the Wakandans.
Yeah, we've been
on every one of them
since they took out our ship.
That's why I wanted you here.
You're lookin' good.
Oh. Well, I try.
- You put
that home gym in?
- Yeah. Last year.
Maybe I'll drop by sometime
and jump on your Peloton.
Howdy.
-I'm special agent in charge.
-Oh, good for you.
You wanna walk me through
the evidence here, or what?
-Yeah. Okay. After you.
-Yeah. Okay.
-All right.
-So, what happened here?
Um, we think
it was a car crash,
but we're having trouble
finding the cars.
- What do you mean?
It was just like this
when you found it?
- Yes.
We think someone involved
got rid of the vehicles.
Got rid of them how?
- They dumped
them into the river.
You're kidding me.
It's got an MIT sticker on it.
I want that transferred
to the NSA immediately.
Hey, Ross?
You got a full tank of gas?
Can you give me a ride
back to Langley?
It's an eight-hour drive.
- Yeah.
We can talk about the case.
Actually, wouldn't mind...
apologizing to you
for a couple of things I said
during our marriage.
- They were blue.
And they had
superhuman strength.
And they came from the water
on the backs of whales.
I struck down three of them
with blows
that should've killed them,
but they rose again.
I wish to leave immediately
to retrieve our princess.
- Okoye,
you will be
stripped of your rank
as General of Wakanda's armies
and your status
as Dora Milaje.
You may.
I have given everything.
Let me die saving my country
and that throne.
Allow me
to make this right.
"Make it right"?
I do not know if my daughter
is alive or dead.
Perhaps we are being
too hasty.
M'- Mmm.
She raised a spear against
her own husband for Wakanda.
Where is her
treacherous husband now
but in a place where she can
visit if she wished? Mine...
is with the ancestors.
I am Queen of the most
powerful nation in the world,
and my entire family is gone!
Have I not given everything?
On your feet, General.
I stood by you
after Killmonger
took the throne,
and you and the elders
in this room stood by him
while I ran begging
to the Jabari for protection.
And I warned you
about taking my daughter
on this mission,
and you lost her.
So, today,
I am done.
Are you here, GRIOT?
- Yes, my Queen.
Were you with Shuri
when she was abducted?
- I was.
Are you able to track
her Kimoyo Beads?
- Ballistics found
slugs all over Cambridge.
Those Wakandans really
took a tour of the city.
- Hmm.
I can't see how
they figured out who built it.
That information
is highly classified.
What is that?
-That's a new ringtone?
-Oh, shit.
Uh, Director, I'm sorry.
I'm gonna have to take this.
It's enough
with the titles.
Just take it. I don't care.
Hey, honey sweetheart.
Ooh.
Uh, no, I'm...
I'm with my boss. Now.
Actually, she's leaving.
All right.
I'm gonna work from home,
and then have a shower.
Everett Ross.
Queen Ramonda?
What are you doing
with Shuri's Kimoyo Beads?
I didn't know they were hers.
All right?
I just found them
at a pretty ugly crime scene.
Do you have the student?
Shuri was trying to save her
when they were both taken.
What? Taken by who?
My agency assumes it was you.
And I'm worried
they might be onto the fact
that I pointed Shuri and Okoye
in the right direction.
Look, if they're in danger,
I wanna help.
But I can't if I don't know
what's going on.
I am afraid there is
a new world power at play.
A country
that's already on our radar?
Or you mean someone else?
- That is all I can say for now.
Please,
alert me if your government
decides to act
on their suspicions.
Yeah. Sure.
Uh, look, if there's anything
I can do to help, let me know.
I owe Shuri my life.
GRIOT, did Shuri have
her earrings with her?
- I lost track of them
in the North Atlantic,
but the people who took her
spoke Yucatec Mayan.
-Hmm?
-- Oui, Miss Nakia.
Queen Mother.
Everything is a lesson here
for the children.
They painted the walls,
they feed the fish,
and they grow
everything we eat here.
I recognize
some of the concepts here.
But you are using
different material.
Yes, we use strictly what
we can find here in Haiti.
You were missed
at T'Challa's funeral.
Oh...
Queen Mother.
- It's been six years
since you left us.
I thought you would at least
come back for the ceremony.
I was afraid
of how final
the funeral would be.
Nakia, daughter of Yaa,
wherever you go,
you are still Wakandan,
and you know
death is not the end.
How is everyone at home?
Shuri has been taken.
What?
You have infiltrated
many nations before.
I was a different person then.
I need someone who can find
where she is being held,
and rescue her,
without being seen.
Who on earth would risk war
with Wakanda?
- Oh, my God.
- Okay, breathe. Breathe.
Oh, don't tell me to breathe.
Where the hell are we?
We're in a cave.
I'm not sure where.
Oh, my God!
What is that?
- Glow worms.
Their larva gives off light.
-- Just calm down.
Okay, is there, like,
a new Black Panther
that you can call
to come and get us?
No.
Why not?
Because it doesn't
work like that anymore.
The Black Panther is gone.
So y'all stopped
having Black Panthers
when I get kidnapped?
Do you understand her?
Not completely.
Nuh-uh.
That is some supervillain shit
right there.
That's in every movie.
Princess Leia.
Belle from
Beauty and the Beast.
That white chick
from Indiana Jones.
It's fine.
You should see what I have
to wear at Warrior Falls.
Wait.
You're not leaving me in here,
are you?
I'm coming back.
Stay calm.
Princess.
Welcome.
Please, feel free.
This is beautiful.
That was my mother's.
These are all
Mesoamerican artifacts.
Most likely 16th century.
Have you been alive
since then?
Your mother was human.
She was.
Then she became
something else.
-How?
-"How?"
"How" is never
as important as "why."
- My mother
and her village
were driven from their farms
by Spanish conquistadors
who brought the smallpox,
a hateful language,
and dogma from another world.
Facing starvation,
war, and disease,
my people turned to Chaac...
our god of rain and abundance.
Chaac gave our shaman
a vision...
-...a way to save his people.
- Chaac led him to a plant
sprouting from a blue rock.
My mother was pregnant with me
at the time,
and she did not want to
ingest the plant
for fear
of what it may do to me.
But the Shaman was convincing.
They all fell sick.
And their lives,
their existence there,
ended.
The plant took away
their ability to breathe air
but enabled them
to draw oxygen from the sea.
They settled in the ocean,
away from war and diseases.
My mother
gave birth to me there
and I became
the firstborn son of Talokan.
The plant gave me wings
on my ankles
and ears
that pointed to the clouds.
I was a mutant.
I could swim in the sky
and age slower.
Breathe the air
our ancestors breathed.
As she grew older,
my mother mourned the life
on land that she once knew...
and died with a broken heart.
She made me promise
to bury her
in the soil of her homeland.
Nothing could prepare me
for what I found there.
Huh?
A Spanish man
of faith cursed me.
As he died by my hand,
he called me...
The child without love.
And I took my name from there.
"Namor."
Because I have no love
for the surface world.
Why are you telling me
all of this?
So that you can understand why
I have to kill the scientist.
What if we took her
to Wakanda?
Let us go.
I give you my word.
She will remain in my country.
I cannot risk that, Princess.
Then keep me instead.
I'd love to see your nation.
Well, you can't go
down there in that.
Hypothermia will grip you
almost instantaneously.
Your blood will become toxic
and the pressure of the ocean
will break every bone
in your body.
Or you can wear a suit.
We have some of them. Come on.
Stay close.
- Hey! Namor, wait!
- Whoa!
Hello.
It's beautiful.
It's made of vibranium.
- Yes.
In the depths of the ocean,
I brought the sun
to my people.
I know you wished me
to spare the life
of the scientist.
But now you see
what I have to protect.
- Nakia,
your hunch was correct.
I have picked up a location
on Shuri's Kimoyo earrings.
- The signal is coming
from an underwater cavern
approximately 140 meters
below the surface.
Queen Mother,
I've found her signal.
It's coming
from an underwater cave.
If she's down there,
I'm sure
I'll encounter resistance.
How would you like me
to proceed?
Retrieve the princess
by any means necessary.
I will attempt
to draw Namor out.
You are the first person
from the surface
to come to Talokan.
Please take this as a token
of our gratitude.
It was made with the plant
that saved Talokan.
You are young, Princess.
When you age as I do,
you realize
we all lose everyone we love.
But when I lost my brother,
it just felt different.
He suffered in silence.
When he finally asked me
to help him, I couldn't.
How does that make sense
that the ancestors would
give me gifts and skills
to help me save my brother,
and I couldn't?
Why?
I don't have an answer
for that question.
My ancestors would often say,
"Only the most broken people
can be great leaders."
I admire
what you have built here.
And how you've protected
your people.
But as princess of Wakanda,
I will not stand for you
killing that young woman.
My nation will not rest
until I'm returned.
I'm not leaving without her.
We need to find a peaceful way
to resolve this.
It is no longer
about the scientist.
For centuries,
the surface nations
have conquered and enslaved
people like us.
Over resources.
Since the day
I buried my mother,
I have prepared my people
for the time
they will come for us.
And that machine is the sign
that the time is now.
I need to know if Wakanda
is an ally or an enemy.
There is no in-between.
So you plan to wage war
on the entire world,
and you want Wakanda
to help you?
That's madness.
There isn't a nation
that wouldn't plunder Wakanda
if given a chance.
If we make an alliance,
we can protect each other
by striking them first.
Then, when the threat of these
nations has been eliminated,
the scientist will be returned
to Wakanda.
And if Wakanda
does not accept, what then?
The scientist will die.
And Wakanda will be
the first nation to fall.
An attack on my people?
Yes.
And I want you
to listen to me.
Wakanda cannot win a war
with Talokan.
I heard you that night,
with your mother at the river.
You said you wanted
to burn the world.
Let us burn it together.
-
Queen Ramonda
won't sell us any vibranium.
And now they abducted
a young woman
who built the machine.
Yeah, with all due respect,
Riri Williams
is a child prodigy
who was running circles around
all of her professors.
The Wakandans
were recruiting her
as part of their
outreach program.
Nothing more. And then,
you guys send in a SWAT team
under cover of night
to arrest the Crown Princess
of an international
superpower.
The President wants
to take offensive action
against Wakanda.
What type of offensive action?
Destabilization.
Well, Special Officer Ross
is our expert.
So, Ross, what do you think?
My sources are telling me
that there's someone else
out there.
-Another nation?
-- Could be. I don't know.
You've gotta give me
enough time
to investigate this properly,
otherwise we're gonna
find ourselves at war
with a country
whose military capacity
we can't even comprehend.
Director?
I think he's the expert.
I think it would be a mistake
to attack Wakanda.
- Yes?
We have a problem.
Is my daughter alive?
The princess
is alive and well.
She requested
to be taken to Talokan.
She will remain there
for the time being.
What can I offer you
in exchange?
Nothing.
I beg to differ.
The Americans are preparing
to blame Wakanda
for your attack
on their mining ship.
Return my daughter
and the scientist
or I will inform them
of your existence.
If you tell the Americans
about us,
if you try to find us,
or if I discover a single
Wakandan ship in the ocean,
I will kill the princess.
I will come to Wakanda
and I will kill you.
So, what happened?
He wants to go to war
with the surface world,
and asked me to help him.
I need to think.
We ain't never
gettin' out of here.
Ey!
Shuri...
Are you okay?
-Give me your Beads!
-Let's go.
Give me your Beads.
I can save her.
We have to go.
Shuri, I don't know
who this lady is,
but we need to listen to her.
Listen, I hit her
with a sonic round.
It is lethal from this distance.
There is no chance.
You don't understand.
This will mean war.
-We have to go.
-Wait!
Did they hurt you?
No. No.
Thank you.
-GRIOT.
-- Yes, my Queen.
Return us to Wakanda at once.
- Princess,
it is good to have you back.
The city has been on edge
since you left.
Go.
Fortify the sonic barriers
for all waterways.
Princess?
Neka.
Thank the ancestors. Hmm?
I just wanted to return these.
No. Keep them.
Might need them soon.
Did you get that
from down there?
Is it true you saw
an underwater empire?
-Yes.
-- Hmm.
It is beautiful.
But these people
are dangerous, Aneka.
- Mm.
- So,
Miss Riri Williams,
what do you think of Wakanda?
The stories just don't do
this place justice.
It's great.
But I really
would like to go home.
You will need to be patient.
Can I at least call my mom?
- The Princess
has been brought home
by the War Dog Nakia.
Glory to Hanuman.
- Glory to Hanuman.
Mm. The spy saves Wakanda
once again.
The Queen will reward her
with lifetime banishment.
I'm sure of it.
Okoye.
After Thanos' attack,
when you left
without saying a word,
it hurt.
I regret not being there
with all of you.
It was not easy.
He was...
King and Black Panther
to everyone.
But to me...
he was everything.
My T'Challa.
When he was taken away
from me, just like that, I...
I had to step away
and let myself break.
I couldn't just...
keep going as if nothing
had happened, you know.
- Mm-hmm.
We are under attack.
Here.
Are you okay?
Are you all right?
GRIOT, activate the Sunbird.
Shuri, where are you?
Making my way
to the city right now.
Stand down! That is an order!
Mother, I'm with Aneka.
We can provide air support.
- Aneka,
do not let her leave the lab.
Mother, you're...
you're breaking up.
-We can't hear you.
-- Shuri!
Love you. Bye!
You just hung up on the Queen.
I just hung up on my mom.
There's a difference.
Come. Let's go!
Invaders!
-Mama! Mama!
EMTs are suffering
a form of sonic hypnosis.
General, plug your ears.
Yes, my Queen.
-Can I help?
-Come, quickly.
Cross your arms...
Nakia.
The fish man.
- Phambili!
Shit, he's too fast.
He's even faster in the water.
-Activating system override.
-- No.
-Wait! I'll fix it.
-Can't leave you here, Shuri!
- Do you see her?
Yes. Right there.
-Go, child.
Wait, what?
And leave you here?
Run!
Okoye, move now!
She did this.
In one week's time,
I will return
with my entire army
and you will join us
against the surface world,
or I will wash Wakanda
from the face of the Earth.
Mother.
-Keep her back!
-Mother!
-Mama! Mama!
-Bury your dead.
Mourn your losses.
You are queen now.
Mother!
No!
Get off of me!
Mother!
Mama!
Help me!
-- Mama!
Jabariland offers you
their comfort for your loss.
You must mourn her
in accordance to the rituals
of your ancestors.
Do not bury yourself
in your technology.
Why are you here?
I promised your brother
that I would provide you
with counsel
and protection.
But I am in need
of your advice today.
Your tribal elders
have approached me
with a proposition.
They wish to evacuate the city
and set up camp
in Jabariland.
So, now you are keen
to hear from a child
who scoffs at tradition?
M'- Mm.
The world...
The world has taken
too much from you
for you to still be
considered a child.
It is in my people's interest
to know
which way your mind
is leaning.
The elders are desperate.
The city is vulnerable.
If you are to provide
for them,
they will be
in great debt to you.
And what of your heart?
Hmm?
Which way
is your heart leaning?
I just buried the last person
who truly knew me.
My heart was buried with her.
- Oh, man.
Yeah, your olive oil's
about to go bad.
What...
What are you doing here?
I'm hungry. And...
Tragedy strikes
the international community.
Sources can now confirm
that Queen Ramonda,
daughter of Lumumba, has died.
Western allies say
that civil conflict
was the likely cause
of the Queen's...
So...
You have any comment?
I wonder what else your
friends are keeping from you.
What are you talking about?
I have no unsanctioned contact
with the kingdom of Wakanda.
What about the Beads?
What?
The Beads.
I had them bugged
before you
ever even got there.
I've been privy to every
conversation you've had,
including that treasonous call
with the Queen.
May she rest in peace.
But it's good.
Well, for us.
All right. You know what?
The Wakandans saved my life.
-They're a good people.
-Mm-hmm.
You ever thought
for a second
what they could be doing?
Ever thought
what we would be doing
if the US was the only country
in the world with vibranium?
Oh, I actually dream
about that.
Val. Val, please.
It's Director de Fontaine.
Your mother protected me
like I was one of her own.
The least that I could do
is try to return the favor.
We need to find a way
to weaken Namor.
Even weakened,
he's still gonna be a problem.
The Black Panther has never
failed to protect Wakanda.
I thought
the Black Panther was gone.
My brother is dead.
But it doesn't mean
the Black Panther is gone.
GRIOT?
Let's start by running
a comparative analysis
between our attempts
at creating
a synthetic
Heart-Shaped Herb...
and the fibers
from this bracelet.
- Yes, Princess.
Since this was grown
from vibranium-rich soil,
they may share
some base-level similarities
that we can exploit.
- As you wish, Princess.
Please upload
my brother's DNA also.
- Uploading now.
Who do I turn to
When I need saving
'Cause you move mountain
I can't do the same
And did you think about
When you left us
Why doesn't he look like them?
His physiology
is completely different.
None of them fly
or have pointed ears like him.
The women
that were guarding us,
they had water
over their mouths
and on their necks.
He didn't have that.
Several organisms
don't need gills
to extract oxygen
from the water, so...
It's like a jellyfish.
He just absorbs the oxygen
from his skin.
It's a process called
-diffusion.
-Diffusion.
Memories, oh, carry me go
Carry me go, oh, nowhere
Sick and tired of it all
Take me far-away
Mr Dj Gbemi trabaye
Now I no fit trust anybody
Na e make I no fit shout
My body don dey tire eh
Every day that passes
without selecting the ruler
is a day wasted.
We must deal with Namor
before he brings
his warriors back here.
And how are we to deal with
a man with that much power?
In that attack,
before he took out your plane,
he jumped back into the water.
What if that's what
makes him strong?
He's breathing air
and getting oxygen
from the water on his skin.
If we could find a way
to dry his ass out,
he won't be as strong.
Yo, that's it.
GRIOT. We need to convert
the Royal Talon Fighter
into a pervaporation chamber.
Is that even possible?
Yes.
You're going to help us
trap him.
Please show Miss Williams
where she's working.
- Right this way.
- How old were you
when you built
your first machine?
- Three.
My stepdad was a car mechanic.
He wanted to build airplanes.
He gave me these tools
and let me just work it out.
So who taught you
how to do all that you do?
- My big brother.
- I was the tip of
the spear of Wakanda's army.
This is not me.
Besides, I'm a civilian now.
I turned in my weapon.
I built you
a new spear as well.
A new one?
Yes.
What is this contraption's
name anyway?
- The Midnight Angel.
Midnight Angel?
This will even
the odds against them.
Sister, I need you to
be ready when I call you.
Please.
My body don dey tire eh
Make me mara eh
Shuri.
Yes.
How many of these
did you make?
- I looked for you
at the Jabari outpost.
I won't be forced out
of my home.
You have such
a rebellious spirit.
Why did you join the Dora?
Why do you care?
As far as I can see
Na the memories
Wey Dey carry me
From reality
E no require visa
I still have a lot of fight
left in me.
Tell me, Aneka,
daughter of Kyana,
do you still have
some fight left in you?
What do you have in mind?
My body don dey tire eh
Make me mara eh
When my whole world
is set on fire
Don't leave me alone
GRIOT,
what's the confidence rate?
- 98.7%, Princess.
Would you like me to print
the Heart-Shaped Herb?
Thought
you'd be back in Haiti by now.
I'm still Wakandan, you know.
So...
this is what
you've been up to.
Yes.
What you have here, now,
is a chance to restore
Wakanda's protector.
It would be the greatest gift
since Bashenga's discovery.
We'll soon find out. Come.
-GRIOT?
-- Yes, Princess.
- Print it.
- How will we know
if it works?
- If it glows.
I mean,
shouldn't we be
burning incense or something?
Only Bast knows
how the ancestors
will make it to this lab.
Are you sure you don't want me
to bury you?
No.
Need you to have access
to my chest,
just in case
I go through cardiac arrest.
"Cardiac arrest"?
She's joking,
right?
-Right?
Allow this Heart-Shaped Herb
to give you the strength
of the Black Panther
and take you
to the Ancestral Plane.
Mother?
N'Jadaka.
Lil' cousin.
How?
How is never as important
as why, right?
You chose me.
Impossible.
I would never choose you.
Why did you take the Herb?
-To see my family.
-No, that's bullshit.
You didn't believe
the Ancestral Plane was real,
did you?
No.
So, why did you take it, then?
You don't have to lie to me.
So I can be strong.
Strong to do what?
See?
We're more alike
than you think.
I took it to avenge
my ancestors too.
I'm nothing like you.
You took it for yourself,
then destroyed the rest.
Unworthy king,
afraid of being replaced.
Just a coward.
No.
I had the courage to do
what was necessary
to change Wakanda.
How many people
like your scientist
did Wakanda protect
before I took the throne?
Cowards.
That was the Panthers
that came before me,
and before T'Challa.
Don't mention my brother.
You're the reason
why he's dead.
You burnt the Herb,
left us with no protector.
Then Namor struck
and killed my mother.
Their blood is on your hands.
That ain't on me.
And don't you dare
take that away
from your mother.
She sacrificed her life
to protect
a young girl
from the lost tribe.
Your father,
he was a hypocrite.
He would've killed that girl.
Shit, he killed
his own brother.
T'Challa was too noble.
He let the man
who murdered your father live.
And here you stand.
Are you gonna be noble
like your brother
or take care of business...
like me?
- Are you okay?
Who did you see?
No one.
I failed.
-It didn't work.
-Hey, Shuri.
-They abandoned me.
-They would never do that.
I did everything
I was supposed to do.
-I re-created the Herb.
-Okay.
I just did your stupid ritual,
and for what?
-Relax.
-Why didn't they come for me?
Just relax.
- Shit.
Can I get some of that too?
I think...
you're going to need a suit.
- There are more
people coming from the city.
M'- They need more space.
So what?
You are visitors.
It is a wonder how anything
gets done with you people.
-- The princess!
M'- She has done it!
-The Black Panther lives!
Namor believes
Wakanda is on her knees.
Our Queen murdered.
Our capital destroyed.
He believes
we have no protector.
But now...
now is our time to strike.
- How, when we don't
even know how to find him?
We'll bring Namor to us.
-Here, again?
-- No.
A distant location at sea.
M'- All right.
Let's say this does work.
Hmm. Assuming
we can kill this man
who can fly and is potentially
as strong as the Hulk...
is murdering him
the right solution?
You were calling for his head
when his only crime
was intimidation.
What has changed, Lord M'Baku?
His soldiers
did not call him
General or King.
They called him K'uk'ulkan.
What is that?
The feather serpent god.
What?
Do you think because we are
living in the mountains,
we do not have access
to books?
-- Elders,
with your permission,
I would like to talk
with Lord M'Baku alone.
Namor's not finished.
He promised to destroy
the surface world.
Now is our opportunity
to take him.
-What are you afraid of?
-M'- War.
If Namor is indeed
a god to his people,
killing him
will risk eternal war.
- And so what?
Was my mother's life
not worth eternal war?
M'- Of course it was.
Of course she was.
But it is not what she would
have wanted for you.
Hmm?
And it is not what I want...
for my people.
You speak of my mother
as if she's still here.
Of what she would've
wanted for me.
Her hopes and her dreams.
But she's dead.
She's gone!
Namor drowned her,
right in front of me!
So, her dreams,
her goals, her hopes for me...
it doesn't exist.
It doesn't matter anymore.
What matters is what I want,
and what I want is Namor dead!
And you're going
to help me get it.
We leave in the morning.
- Hi.
Good morning.
If we survive this,
I want you to know you have
a home with me in Haiti.
Here. Take my hands.
Shuri, I want you
to be honest with me.
Who did you see
when you took the Herb?
If you go to war
for vengeance,
it will not fill the hole
left from her loss.
It will only grow larger,
and it will consume you.
It already has.
For the Queen.
Phambili!
- Riri,
how's it going up there?
Hey, Mr. GRIOT.
I could really use
that backup right now.
- I thought
you'd never ask.
- Shit.
Shit, he's fast.
But I'm faster.
Whoo!
I got you.
It's on you now, Shuri.
-Princess.
-- No.
I am the Black Panther,
and I'm here for retribution!
- Pervaporation cells
activated.
- What's wrong?
You need a glass of water?
-Yo, we got him.
-Good!
Namor has been captured.
Back to Wakanda!
Move out!
-What is going on?
The sonic emitter
has been destroyed.
That can't be good.
- Panther, the
Sea Leopard has lost power,
and they are experiencing
significant casualties.
Okoye.
- Panther.
Phambili!
Aneka.
Okoye!
It is time.
- Phambili!
For Wakanda!
- Wakanda!
GRIOT, what's the damage?
- Catastrophic.
His spear is made
of raw vibranium.
The ship could explode
at any second.
Get us to the desert.
-- No!
I got you, sis.
Hold on.
- Get off me!
- All right, come here.
M'-
May the ancestors save us
if the princess
does not hurry.
We may be going to join them.
If so, hey,
let us take as many of them
with us as we can.
It could've been different.
Are you gonna be noble
like your brother
or take care of business
like me?
I'm not my brother.
Namor will beg me for mercy
as I stand and watch
as he dies.
-Wakanda forever!
- Shuri.
- Mama.
Show him
who you are.
Yield,
and Wakanda
will protect your oceans.
We will protect your secrets.
Yield,
and your people will live.
Vengeance has consumed us.
We cannot let it
consume our people.
Wakanda forever!
- Wakanda forever!
Oou le le oou le le oou le le
-Oou le le
Oou oou
le le oou le le oou le oou le
Well, I pray that the universe
Thank you, my love.
Gives you way more
than you deserve
When the tears fall
like shooting stars
Remember who you are
Just look up to the sky
You'll see
Well, I pray that the universe
Gives you way more
than you deserve
- Yo.
-All set to head home?
As long as you're sure
the police
won't be waiting for me
at the airport.
Don't worry.
Took care of that.
But you might
want to slow down
on your
homework-for-hire business.
Get caught slipping,
I can't help you with that.
They said you wanted
to talk to me about something?
Yes.
Your suit.
It's a great design,
but can't let you
leave with it.
It's all good.
Figured the least I could do
is help Wakanda
clean up my mess.
I have one more thing
to show you.
Come.
Took me a while to find
all the parts from the river,
but it was worth it.
- How did you...
It's my dad's car.
We used to
work on it before...
Oou le le oou le le oou le le
I'm coming back for you
-You sure this is her?
-Every part.
Have it shipped to Boston.
Be there before you arrive.
Bring it in, man.
- Panther, Miss Williams'
transport has arrived.
Look after yourself.
Sure you're not trying
to slide to Chicago?
Catch a Bulls game?
Sounds fun,
but I have something
I need to take care of.
And now I present to you
Princess Shuri,
the Black Panther!
The Black Panther
sends her regards,
but she will not be
joining us today.
I, M'Baku,
leader of the Jabari Tribe,
son of Wakanda,
wish to challenge
for the throne.
What the hell is this?
-- Can we turn around?
- I don't know, man.
We'll lose an hour.
Why don't you go check it out?
- Okay.
- Yeah,
this is Shauver.
Yeah, looks like we got
a tree blocking our way.
How do you want us to proceed?
-What the...
Ah!
A colonizer in chains.
Now I have seen everything.
Funny.
- Merci.
- Hey.
It's good to see you.
Everything is ready.
Just give me one moment, eh?
Actually,
I think I should do it
on my own.
Of course.
Lift me up
Hold me down
Keep me close
Safe and sound
Burning in a hopeless dream
Hold me when you go to sleep
Keep me in the warmth
of your love
When you depart keep me safe
Safe and sound
Lift me up
Hold me down
Keep me close
Safe and sound
Drowning in an endless sea
Take some time
and stay with me
Keep me in the strength
of your arms
Keep me safe
Safe and sound
Lift me up
Hold me down
Keep me safe
Safe and sound
Burning in a hopeless dream
Hold me when you go to sleep
Keep me safe
We need light
We need love
-Lift me up
In your arms
-Hold me down
-I need love, I need love
I need love
-Keep me safe
-Hold me
We need light
We need love
- Shuri,
can we join you now?
This is my son, Toussaint.
Toussaint,
this is your aunty, Shuri.
Hi.
We agreed it was better
for him to grow up here.
Away from the pressure
of the throne.
Your father,
your baba,
prepared us for his death,
didn't he?
But he didn't want us
to go to the funeral
because he felt the time
was not yet right.
So we had our own ceremony
for him here.
Did my mother meet him?
- She did.
It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Toussaint is a beautiful name.
It holds a great history.
Thanks. Yours is cool, too,
I guess.
My mom says you are good
at keeping secrets.
Is that true?
Yes, I can keep a good secret.
Toussaint is my Haitian name.
My name is Prince T'Challa,
son of King T'Challa.
I give my heart to this place
I give my soul or whatever it takes
Never run away
I've got enough angels to storm the gates
I'm not afraid
Behold the brave
And I'll have it, no other way
I missed the emergence
and these moments of you
The mere reflection of me
That mirror can't change its view
So until those rivers run out
It runs through me wherever you are
I'll be there
We carry on
Born again
I give my heart to this place
I give my whole soul and whatever it takes
Never run away
And I'd relive this
Just to see your face again
I know that you'll do the same
Born again
Just tell me what I need to do
I'd die and come back
just to love you
Just tell me
I'm begging you
Just tell me what I need to do
Oh
Modify by Blue-Bird™